Last time on Zombieland Saga, the others woke up and started acting like people again!
Then it was time for us to start our idol activities.
Or it would have been, but nobody really felt like singing and dancing.
Then there was some drama which made Ai and Junko realize how tough the streets could be for a zombie.
It was mostly just people getting mad at me.
But it all turned out okay, because that gave me the courage to step up to the mic and spit some hot fire!
And that's how we took our first step to becoming a real idol group!
Uh, if you can call us that.
Alright! Good morning again to all you lovely ladies!
Uh, good morning to you! I said good morning to you!
Don't get in her face! You're gonna freak her out!
Straight to business then.
Clearly diving into that Saga Castle show prematurely was reckless.
So I'm going to be blunt.
You girls...
We're absolutely wonderful!
You somehow managed to keep your rotten little secret under wraps,
all the while playing Hot Potato with a disembodied head!
Now that is team spirit!
Your bodies may fall apart, but your hearts stick together!
Which is why I will now bestow my most enthusiastic clapping upon each one of you!
Feel free to join in and applaud your fellow decaying flesh piles on a successful zombying endeavor!
Nice zombying!
And another thing!
Suck it up!
Sir?
Girl you gotta be...
Uh huh...
Those raps were neat...
Yeah yeah...
You brought the heat...
Foo!
Uh...
Yeah...
Don't you dare go getting cocky!
Now that your show is over, you think it's all happy party fun time?
Do not lose sight of our main objective!
Snap those necks back around to what's in front of you!
Just because you're dead doesn't mean you can take your sweet time and relax!
The next task I want you crumbling corpses to tackle is...
One of these...
Gorilla?
He couldn't spell it...
Do forgive me, but what is a gorilla performance?
Um...
You put on a show in public and don't tell anyone about it, so it's like a fun surprise type thing!
Oh...
Like testing your sword on a passerby!
Heh...
Wait, but if we do a street concert, won't the police come after us again?
Not to worry!
As long as you hide your gross faces with makeup, you'll all just get a slap on the wrist!
Don't be such a wimp, Sakura!
We can't just let the pigs ruin our rally, right?
And you won't be able to freestyle your way out of it this time!
I'll make sure you're all pretty and cute and perfect the way an idol group should be!
I'll teach you!
One thing...
Yes, Junko?
It's just...
I've done plenty of solo concerts, but I've never been part of a group before, so I'm a...
A loner!
A loner?
You're a lonely little loser!
Anyway, the performance will be tomorrow morning in the plaza by Karatsu Station.
Tomorrow?
We can't learn a whole song and the choreography with just one practice day!
Guess you're gonna have to pull an all-nighter then!
I mean, what are you gonna do? Die from lack of sleep?
Ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Woo...
Ha...
You
Damn, I had no idea how much crap you're supposed to memorize when you're an idol.
Yeah, but learning new things is good for you.
What's with the racket, Squirt?
My name's not Squirt.
I'm the shining star of stage and screen, Miss Lily Hoshikawa.
Pain in the ass.
Did you want to say something?
Before we practice, I think we should pick a leader.
Leader?
Yeah!
Somebody's got to be in charge of us.
That way there's always someone to make the tough decisions.
In that case, I think it would be a good idea for one of our more experienced idols to be the...
Out of the question.
I'm the first captain of Dorami, the legendary all-female biker gang from Saga Prefecture.
The name is Saki ni Kaido!
I did a damn good job bossing all those biker chicks around!
So wrangling a bunch of baby dolls like you will be a walk in the park!
I pick me!
Geez, we heard ya.
Who wants to fight me for captain?
Looks like it's just you.
Aw, yeah!
We're coming to get you, Japan!
You want to start with Kyushu?
It's leader, not captain.
This isn't a biker gang.
Leader!
We need a group name!
Huh?
We don't have one?
You mean like Death Musume and Greenface?
None of Tatsumi's dumb ideas are idly enough!
That's a good point.
How about this one?
We could be magical cutie Lily is a lily ass!
That's a lot of lily.
I'm not gonna spend eternity with a kiddie ass group name like that.
I was thinking something more like this.
Could you read that out loud?
Says Joan of Arc!
Does it?
I think it has a noble ring to it.
You do?
She gets what I'm talking about!
However, perhaps this would serve us.
Amiibu wolves?
Hey, that's pretty awesome!
As if.
They'd visit me.
Back in Shimabara.
Oh, no fair, you guys!
I want to be called something cuter!
I also do need to be cute.
Why, you little...
Hey, Ty?
We're trying to have a conversation here.
Don't put that in your mouth!
It can kill you!
For the last time, we're zombies.
Oh, please!
No!
Oh, this is getting ridiculous.
Figure it out, Sakura.
Huh?
But why me?
Because I said so?
Well, let me think here.
Oh, how about Frambois?
Oh, that's really cute!
Frambo-what now?
Oh, that's kind of hard to read.
A badass logo is half the battle.
You took a cute word and made it look stinky.
Well, we are dead, so I'm sure we do have a terrible stench.
Let's get back to that group name.
Any more?
I bet Sakura's got some.
Let's see.
How does French high sound?
Not that, but it should be something French.
French bread, French fries, French toast.
What else is from France?
Cream puffs?
Russ!
Oh, dear.
Ew, she's all inky!
She's sneezing from the marker?
Ah, sissy!
You okay, Tai?
I get it now.
What?
Am I missing something here?
I don't think Tai was just sneezing.
Really?
I mean, she is, but it's more than that.
Ah, sissy!
You see?
We needed a new name, and she picked the perfect one!
From Shushu!
Doesn't it sound so pretty and cool?
From Shushu?
Yeah, you like it?
From Shushu.
You know, I don't hate it.
Indeed.
It is quite an elegant name.
So cute, right?
It's way better than what he came up with.
From Shushu.
Wow, the more you say it, the more adorable it sounds.
You did a great job, Tai.
From Shushu.
Yep, looks good to me.
I'll write it like that.
Have it your way.
All right, it's official.
From now on, the seven of us are going to be called Frans Shushu.
Now we just need to actually learn the song for tomorrow.
Right!
Sweet!
Here we go, Frans Shushu!
It's time to practice till our butts fall off!
You ready?
Hey!
Yeah!
I don't think we can do this.
It's way too hard.
I thought I was starting to understand, but singing and dancing are way tougher than I thought.
If we blow it, we're done for.
There's just not enough time.
I and Junko are the only ones who know what they're doing.
Tai?
We haven't even pulled it off once during practice, and tomorrow we'll have an audience.
We're about to get thrown off.
I don't want to!
I should have thought about this logically.
Being zombies is crazy enough, but zombie idols?
Frans Shushu!
Get off that thing now!
Still though, I have to see this through.
I want to relive that feeling I had the first time I was on stage, and figure out what it was.
Frans Shushu!
Sakura!
Are you okay?
I'm going back in, so I can practice some more.
Whoa.
Saki, Lily, Tai, even though we're zombies now,
as long as everybody works hard.
I know we have a chance to achieve our-
Shame on you!
Whatever happened to practicing?
I'm confident that even though we're zombies now,
if we work hard, it'll be possible for us to achieve our mission.
Um, that's what I was about to-
Yugiri's right.
We don't need your negativity.
But-
Yeah, she knew just what to say to get us all motivated!
Hmph.
Cool.
They've been gone a while.
Hmm.
Yugiri was supposed to bring the girls back here.
Do you think they gave up?
I think it might be better if they did.
You can't pull off an idle performance overnight.
Besides, if the show doesn't go well,
then the audience won't have a good time.
If it's from the heart, they'll still appreciate it.
But that's if.
All right, let's get crackin'!
We're gonna put on a damn good show tomorrow!
Yeah!
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, and four.
And one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
One, two.
Oh, Lily!
Are you hurt?
The steps for this part are so tricky.
Then try dancin' better.
Wow, thanks for the tip!
Stop bickering, both of you!
Sorry.
Well, I think we should keep practisin' with or without him.
Come on, girls, let's try again.
I'll start the song.
What?
If you don't dance, then you're just plain old zombies.
Being an idol is hard.
You don't understand.
Oh, cry me a river.
I'm telling you, there's no way this'll work!
Is that what you honestly believe?
Trust me, I know.
Then why were you two idols when you were alive?
You're dead, but at least the others are trying to live.
Will you join them?
Or would you rather just sit and rot?
Okay, is everybody ready?
Ready?
Starting now, you're a guerrilla squadron,
boldly prowling through the ruthless concrete jungle.
This train station is your battleground
where you will unleash confusion and wonderment
upon the passerby,
so as to claim victory!
All right, ladies, time's a way stand.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I... Junko...
Sakura!
I guess the show will have to go on without them.
Okay. This is our chance to make those practice hours count.
Uh, hey everybody! We're from Shushu!
We worked hard on this solo! We hope you like it!
Awaken returner, let your heart feel desire.
We're longing for miracles that can inspire.
Hey, look! Is she singing with squid in her mouth?
Oh, she is! But why?
Once upon a time my dreams were bright and colorful
But then reality set in and everything was dull
Was dull, now those dreams are coming
I wonder how everyone is feeling
I think they're okay
And then I wake up in the light
Gotta get it right if we're gonna survive
Never gonna stop when the dead are alive
Living life the best we can
Going down our destined path
Ah, how do I go on?
How do I try?
Don't give up, all you need is right beside you
You'll see if you just look around
Around, around, around, around
Around, around, around, it's right, we're with you
What?
Don't stop singing, you idiot
You okay?
Sorry, I didn't mean to
I didn't rehearse enough
Whoops
Stay calm
We can do it, guys
To all the fears you have
Say bye, bye, bye
You've got this
You'll promise it's your turn
For now, all we need to do is put our hearts into this
And try our hardest
Cut in
Here we go
Time for the final verse
Oh no, what are the words again?
I forgot
What do I do?
Come on, brain
Please don't do this to me
Ah, how can I go on, I'm so afraid
Don't give up, your anxiety's a liar
No time to stop, you gotta
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight
Awaken returner, let your heart feel courage
Let's rise up and show the world how we can go, go, go, go high, high, high, high, high
Awaken returner, let your heart feel desire
A longing for miracles that can inspire
Excitement, take joy wherever you can
Give it to me
Be boring and grabbing, don't back down
You've got it to all the doubt
That girl, she's having a blast
Our passion, keep her smile
Our deepest emotions
Our souls will bear when we sing
Cut in
Is it over?
We should sign off
Yeah
Anyway
Hey, uh, we're from Shushu
Thanks a lot
We'll put on a better show next time, I promise
I'll see you then
There you are
Let's go
That was fun
Well, that could have gone a hell of a lot better, huh?
Hold it right there, ladies
Hate to tell you, but you can't do street shows without a permit
What are you trying to do here, get arrested?
Because I will arrest ya
You'll never take me alive
No, ladies, now isn't the time
Dad, you're the leader
Um, sorry, officer, we'll leave right away
Hey, you look familiar
Me?
Uh, no, I don't
Go, go, go, go
Go, go, go
Too much of the old charm
We still ended up performing, huh
Hey guys, can we talk?
Thank you really
If it hadn't been for you nobody would have stayed through the whole song
That all?
Both of you did an amazing job. You totally saved the show
It made me feel like the rest of us might not ever make it as idols without you
No, wait, I mean because of that I want to practice even harder
I know we might not be real idols yet and we're zombies too, which just makes everything that much trickier
But I'll give it my very best and if each of us does that then despite what we're up against
I'm sure fran shushu can become something really incredible in the future. I
Think that's how we all feel
Have a good night
You know it today was a total disaster
But performing with everyone felt so much better than I ever thought it would
You were great too
Harness heal the deepest whine they lose
Our chapter has ended, but we'll be all right
Keep your gaze ahead and walk toward the light
Now it's time we say good-bye
But don't forget that we're starting over from scratch
You
Junko here. Singing is my greatest passion.
Is this my chance to return to the stage and feel the glow of the spotlight?
Next time on Zombieland Saga, Episode 4, Warming Dead Saga.
Hope you like it.